Edna O'Brien papers, circa 1939-2000
Emory University
- Correspondence, 1939-2000, Series 1; Boxes 1-18
  - Alphabetical correspondence, 1955-2000, Subseries 1.1; Boxes 1-12
    - Johnson, Richard, undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Johnston, Denis, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Jones, Gordon, undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Jones, Jack, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Jones, Penny, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Jones, Peter, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Jong, Erica, 1997-1999 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Joseph, Robert L., 1968 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Journal of Beckett Studies, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - J-unidentified (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Kabbani, Rana, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Kamal, Aleph, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Kane, Michael, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Kantzuer, Dieter, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Karlsson, Mats, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Kaufman, Phil, 1992-1998 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Keane, John B., 1999 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Keane, Nora, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Keay, Douglas, 1955-1960 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Kehae, Kerry, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Kelly, David, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Kelly, Kevin, undated (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Kelly, Terry, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Kennedy, Caroline, undated (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Kennedy, Ellen, undated (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Kennedy, Edward (Ted), undated (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Kennedy, Philippa, undated (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Kennedy, Richard, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Kennedy, William, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Kenney, Anthony, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Kenny, Sean, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Keogh, Lainey, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Kershaw, Richard, undated (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Kersnowski, Alice Hughes, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Key, Lynn, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Kiely, Ben, undated (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Kilroy, John, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Kimberg, Jud, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Kimmins, Fiona, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - King, Grace, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - King, Peter, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Kinlay, Howard, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Kinnock, Neil, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Kinseida Ltd., 1967 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Kirchwey, Karl, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - K.I.S.S., 1995 (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - Kissinger, Henry and Nancy, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Knights, L.C., 1993 (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - Knopf, Alfred, 1959-1973 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Kohner, Paul, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - Konchalovsky, Andrei, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Konecky, Ronald, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Koninklijke Uitgeverij Erven JJ Tijl N.V., 1965 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - Kosinski, Jerzy, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - Kubrick, Stanley, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - Kurtz, Irma, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - K-unidentified (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - La Sainte Union Convent, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Lagerfeld, Karl, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Lahti, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Lambert, Catherine, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Lamia, Peter, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Lan, David, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Landers, Hal, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Lane, Margaret, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Lasky, Melvin, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Lawson, J.J., 1967 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Lemon, Gerard, 1986-1995 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Lerner, Alan and Liz, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Lescher, Robert, 1976-1979 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Lescher, Susan, 1979-1989 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Liddy, John, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Lindstrom, Jeremy, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Lister, Monica, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Little, Brown and Co., 1976 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Little, Peter, undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Littlewood, Joan, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Lloyd, John, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Logan, Joshua, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - London Films, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - London Weekend Television, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Longmans, Green, and Co., Ltd., 1967 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Lord John Press, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Losey, Joseph, 1964-1970 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Loughman and Co., 1998 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Loughrby, Dan, undated (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Low, Sally, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Luddy, Tom, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Ludford, Kathy, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - L-unidentified (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Mac Liammoir, Micheal, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - MacBride, Sean, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - MacDonogh, Steve, 1995-1997 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - MacEntee, Patrick, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - MacGregor, Jimme, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Mackey, Jim, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - MacLehose, Christopher, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - MacLeod, Joan, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Macnamara, Jimmy, undated (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Mademoiselle, 1962-1963 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - The Magazine of the Arts, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Magee, Patrick, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Mailer, Norman, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Mainhall, Margaretta, undated (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Major, John, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Malamud, Bernard, 1961-1962 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Malkovich, John, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Mallon, Seamus, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Manhattan Theatre Club, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Mann, Christopher, 1961-1968 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Mann, Stanley, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Manville, W.H., undated (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Marcus, David, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Marks, Karen, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Marr, David, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Marsden, Hazel, undated (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Martin, Alan, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - Martin, JoAnn, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - Martin, Neil, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - Martin, Reginald, undated (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - Martin Secker and Warburg Ltd., 1964 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - Maschler, Tom, 1961-1968 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - Mason, Patrick, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - Mathers, Marian, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - Matheson, Ormsby, Prentice, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 68)
    - Mathias, Sean, 1982-1994 (Box 7, Folder 69)
    - Maul, Tim, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 70)
    - Mayer, Peter, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 71)
    - McBurney, Simon, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 72)
    - McCann, Colum, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 73)
    - McCann, Elizabeth Ireland, undated (Box 7, Folder 74)
    - McCartney, Paul, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - McCauley, Bernadette, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 76)
    - McConnell, Turlough, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 77)
    - McCourt, John, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 78)
    - McCulloch, Joseph, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 79)
    - McDowall, Roddy, undated (Box 7, Folder 80)
    - McEvoy, Frank, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 81)
    - McGlashan, Alan, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 82)
    - McGlinchey, Declan, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 83)
    - McGlinchey, Dominic, undated (Box 7, Folder 84)
    - McGlinchey, Mary, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 85)
    - McGuinness, Paul, undated (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - McHenry, Maureen, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 87)
    - McIntosh, Mavis, 1961-1963 (Box 7, Folder 88)
    - McIntosh, McKee, and Dodds Inc., 1965-1967 (Box 7, Folder 89)
    - McKellen, Ian, 1977-1999 (Box 7, Folder 90)
    - McKenna, P.J., 1998 (Box 7, Folder 91)
    - McKeone, Gary, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 92)
    - Medina, Kate, 1976-1979 (Box 7, Folder 93)
    - Mellen, Joan, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 94)
    - Mendoza, June, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 95)
    - Merikangas, James, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 96)
    - Merle, Roger, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 97)
    - Merrick, Dave, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 98)
    - MGM Studios, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 99)
    - Miles, Bernard, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 100)
    - Miller, Henry, 1972-1978 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Minnikin, Liz, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Mitchell, Jennie, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Mohr, Jean, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Monaghan, Ken, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Monteitti, Charles, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Moody, Gil, 1996-1998 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Mooney, Ria, 1960-1968 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Moore, Deborah, 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Moran, Barney, 1967-1969 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Moreno, Doloros Kaloper, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Morgan, Dylan, undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Moriarty, A.P., 1967 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Morrey, Jonathan, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Morrison, Blake, undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Morrison, Danny, 1994-1997 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Mortimer, Sir John, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Mortimer, Penny, undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Moseley, Walter, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - The Mostyn Bureau, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Mostyn-Owen, Orlando, undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Mouret, Suzanne, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - MPO Pictures, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Mulligan, Kate, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Murphy, Richard, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Murphy, Yvonne, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Murray, Hughs Wolfe, undated (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Murray, Father Raymond, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Murray, Tony, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - M-unidentified (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Nathan, Monique, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - National Library for the Blind, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - National Secular Society, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - National Theatre, 1986-1999 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Nault, Marianne, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Negrisolo, Gabriella, undated (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Nelligan, Kate, 1984-1986 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Nellings, Solveig, 1968-1975 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Neville, Richard, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - The New American Library, Inc., 1966 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - The New English Library, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - New Republic, undated (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - New Statesman, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - The New York Times, 1980-1995 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - New York Times Book Review, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - The New Yorker, 1960-1999 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Newman, Alexander, 1990-1996 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Newman Society, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Nichols, Mike, 1970-1985 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Nicolson, Nigel, 1976-1999 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Nilsson, Leopoldo Torre, undated (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Nixon, Nicholas, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - Noone, John, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Norris, David, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Norris, Gabriella and Maxwell, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Nottingham, Nadiya Peters, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Nova, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - Nystroinn, Marita, 1961-1962 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - N-unidentified (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - O’Brien, Jack, 1994-1998 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - O’Brien, Joan, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - The Observer, 1961-1971 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - O’Byrne, Charles John, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - O’Connell, Patricia, 1987-1999 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - O’Donovan, Joan, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - O’Dwyer, Pat, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - O’Flanagan’s Bookshop, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - O'Hara, Michael, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Ohilbaum, Isolde, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Okrent, Daniel, undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Oliver, Michael, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Olivier, Laurence and Family, 1981-1999 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - O’Mordha, Sean, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Onassis, Jaqueline Kennedy, 1990 and undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Ondaatje, Michael, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Orchover, Alan, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Orion House, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Orion Publishing Group, 1995-1999 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Osborne, John, 1963-1981 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - O'Sullivan, Jim, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Otto, Donald, undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Over 21, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Owen, Peter, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Oxford Union Society, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Oxford University Press, 1994-1995 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Oz Publications Ink Ltd., 1971 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - O-unidentified (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Page, Anthony, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Pagoda, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Pakula, Hannah, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Palos, Marta, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Parker, Lynne, undated (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Parkinson, Cecil, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Patterson, Dick, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Pearson Television, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Peckham School, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - PEN American Center, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Pen/Faulkner Award, 1995-1997 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Penguin Books Ltd., 1964-1999 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Penthouse, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Penycate, John, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Pieraccini,. Rolando, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Pilkington, Maureen, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Pinter, Lady Antonia and Harold, 1971-1999 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Pitts, Helen, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Plaistowe, Richard, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - The Poetry Center, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Porter, David, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Porter, Thea, undated (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Powell, Simon, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Priestley, D.E., 1961 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Priestley, J.B., 1961 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Projection Room, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Pujman, Petr, 1961-1967 (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Puttnam, David, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Puttnam, Patricia, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - P-unidentified (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Queen, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - The Queen's University of Belfast, 1998-1999 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Quinn, John, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Quinn, Victor, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Q-unidentified (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Radio Taxi of London, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Rae, Douglas, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Rajendla, Cecil, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Ramstedt, Lillemor, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Random House Inc., 1960-1962 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Rapp, Helen, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Rawlinson, Sir Peter, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Recorded Picture Company, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Rediffusion Television Limited, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Redmer, Bessie C., 1967 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Reenpaa, Erkki, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Reihall, Dorine, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Reihall, Ramona, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Remfry, David, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Remnick, David, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Remy, Michele, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Reynolds, Sheldon, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Richardson, Jean, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Richardson, Maurice, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Richardson, Stewart, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Richardson, Tony, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Rickman, Alan, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Rimmer, Gordon S., 1967 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Risler, Walt, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Robbins, Jerome, 1966-1989 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Robins, Davies, and Little Ltd., 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Robinson, Mary, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Roddam, John, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Rodgers, Iain, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Rodman, Judy, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Roest, Hans, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Rogers, Deborah, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Rogers, Joyce, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Rogers, Peter, 1993-1995 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Rogow, Arnold, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Rosen, Arlene Dahl, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Rosenberg, Max, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Rosenstore, Howard, undated (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Rosenthal; Haas and Co., 1988-1999 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Roth, Philip, 1984-1999 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Rotha, Paul, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Rothfield, Steven, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Rous, Mary, undated (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Rowe, Dorothy, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Rowohlt Verlag Gmbh, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Roy, Harcourt, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - Royal Court Theatre, 1967-1997 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Royal Shakespeare Theatre, 1981-1986 (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - RTE, 1966-1999 (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Russell, Bertrand, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Russell, Claire, 1965-1998 (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Russell, Leonard, 1964-1976 (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Russell, Mary, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Russell and Volkening, Inc., 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - Rutt, Ellen Keane, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Ryan, E.J., 1994 (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Ryan, Phyllis, undated (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - Rybarova, Melanie, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Ryder, Angharan, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - R-unidentified (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - Saatchi, Maurice and Josephine, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Sacks, Oliver, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Salinger, J.D., 1968 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Salmon, Nick, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Sampson, Denis, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - San Francisco Chronicle, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Sarbach, Hugo, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Sawicki, Yan Adam, 1992-1995 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Sayers, Michael, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Schatzman, Morton, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Schaub, Martin, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Schiffman, Sunny Rogers, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Schlesinger, Arthur, 1989-1999 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Schnack, Elisabeth, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Schuchard, Ronald, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Schull Books, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Scott, Michael, undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Scott, Nicholas, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Scott-Gvay, Adam, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Screen Gems, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Seale, Patrick, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Seaton, Estella, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Seattle Repertory Theatre, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Seidel, Ernst, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - The Selina Scott Show, undated (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Sellers, Catherine, undated (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Selwyn, Charlotte, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Senn, Fritz, 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Serventy, Vincent, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Shakespeare and Company, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Shaw, Fiona, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Shaw, Sam, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Sheil, Anthony, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Shelbourne Hotel, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Shephard, Sam, undated (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Shore, Nancy, 1986-1988 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Show, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Shubik, Irene, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Shulman, Alexandra, undated (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Sigmund, Elizabeth, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Simon and Schuster Inc., 1964-1999 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Simon, Carly, undated (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Simon, Jean-Daniel, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Simpson, Alan, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Simpson, John Blake, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Singer, Isaac B., 1971 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Skeffington, Owen Sheehy, 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Skinner, Knute, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Slack, Tim, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Slattery, J.M., 1967 (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - Slimming Magazine Limited, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - Smithy, Peter Donal, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - Snowdon, Tony and Lucy, undated (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - Solas anois, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - Spearman, John, undated (Box 11, Folder 55)
    - The Spectator, 1992-1999 (Box 11, Folder 56)
    - Spoto, Donald, 1995-1997 (Box 11, Folder 57)
    - Spurrier, Steven, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 58)
    - St. James Press, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 59)
    - Stacy, Donald, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 60)
    - Starke, Pam, 1988-2000 (Box 11, Folder 61)
    - Steven, Stewart, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 62)
    - Stevenson, Juliet, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 63)
    - Stewart, Bruce, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 64)
    - Stoble, Cheryl, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 65)
    - Strach, Walter, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 66)
    - Strachan, Pat, 1993-1997 (Box 11, Folder 67)
    - Straus, Peter, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 68)
    - Straus, Roger, 1993-1996 (Box 11, Folder 69)
    - Strauss, Helen, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 70)
    - Streep, Meryl, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 71)
    - Struven, Peter, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 72)
    - Sunday Mirror, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 73)
    - The Sunday Telegraph, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 74)
    - The Sunday Times, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 75)
    - Svensson, Elisabeth, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 76)
    - Sweeney, Francis, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 77)
    - Swift Tercentenary Committee, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 78)
    - S-unidentified (Box 11, Folder 79)
    - Tatler, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Taylor, A.W., 1963 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Taylor, Nelson, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Taylor, Seamus, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Tahicai, Annette, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Temple, Robert, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Thames Television Limited, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Theroux, Paul, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Thompson, Bill, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Thompson, Peter, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Thomson, Hamish, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Thornley, Grant R., 1964-1965 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Tierny, J.G., undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - The Times Literary Supplement, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Tolkshand, Clifford, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Touitt, Gillian, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Towers Hotel, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Triska, Jan, 1965-1968 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Trudeau, Pierre Elliott, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Turley, Tom, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Tyegard, Anders, undated (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Mark Twain Journal, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Twentieth Century Fox Film Corp., 1965 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Tyler, Diana, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Tynan, Kenneth, 1961-1969 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Tyzack, Maggie, undated (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - T-unidentified (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - The Unterberg Poetry Center (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Van de Kamp, Peter, 1996-1997 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Vanson Productions, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Vasturo, Margaret, undated (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Viera, Marianne, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Viking Press, undated (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - V-unidentified (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Waldron, Reg, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Wallencheck, Laura, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Walsh, Bernard, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Walsh, Caroline, undated (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Walsh, George, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Wanzenberg, Alan, undated (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Warner Books, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Warner, Deborah, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Warren, E.W., 1962 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Watson, George, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Weber, Bruce, undated (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Weidenfeld and Nicolson, 1969-1999 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Weir, Peter, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Weir, Veronica, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Weissberger, Arnold, 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - Wells, Linda, 1992-1995 (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - Wesker, Arnold, 1959-1969 (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - White, Michael, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - White, P.A., 1963 (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - White, Patrick, 1960-1966 (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - Whitney Museum of American Art, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - The Whoseday Book, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - Whyte, Michael, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - Wiles, Peter, 1965-1968 (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - Wilkins, David, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 59)
    - Willett, Louisa, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 60)
    - William, Geoffrey, undated (Box 12, Folder 61)
    - Williamson, Henry, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 62)
    - Willingham, Calder, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 63)
    - Wilson, Sir Harold, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 64)
    - Wintour Family, undated (Box 12, Folder 65)
    - Wishart, Michael, undated (Box 12, Folder 66)
    - Woman's Own, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 67)